Assignment_4_Answers:

1. What other stuff does read.csv() do automatically?
-reads the data in as a data frame
-row.names is not specified, the first column is taken to be row names.
It also assumes a field or line is blank if there is nothing put before a character or the end of the line.
It also determines the number of columns by looking at the first 5 lines of input.


2. How is it different from read.csv2()?
	read.csv and read.csv2 are identical to read.table except for the defaults. They are intended for reading ‘comma separated value’ files (‘.csv’) or (read.csv2) the variant used in countries that use a comma as decimal point and a semicolon as field separator. Similarly, read.delim and read.delim2 are for reading delimited files, defaulting to the TAB character for the delimiter. Notice that header = TRUE and fill = TRUE in these variants, and that the comment character is disabled.

This is different from .csv() because it requires the column sign(;) instead of the comma (,) to separate values. Also, this uses commas for decimal notation.
	•	3. Why does read.csv2() even exist?
	Probably to deal with data gathered from other countries that used commans instead of periods for decimal notation. 


4. How could I change the parameters of read.csv() to make it so the class of the “State” column is “factor” instead of “character?”
	By changing the paramenter of colClasses inside .csv as showned: 


df <- read.csv("../../Data/landdata-states.csv", colClasses = c("factor","character","numeric","integer","integer","integer","numeric","numeric","numeric","integer","integer")) 


5. What command would give the summary stats for ONLY the Home.Value column?
	summary (df$Home.Value)


6. What value is returned by the command: names(df)[4] ?
[1] "Home.Value"


7. What is happening when you add (…col=df$region) to the above plotting code? In other words, what happens when you run: plot(x=df$Year,y=df$Land.Value,col=df$region)

	Adds the color, and then the factor assign a number for each one of the values of regions. 
Ultimately, the colors are changed into regions. 


